The End
Thanks to my father, I was able to create Generated songs.
Thank you very much.
This is the first time I've seen pitch black.
I have never seen this video before,
I'm shooting my first video
I'm shooting my first video.
Thank you very much.
It's called a kumquat.
It's called a kink.
This is ideal.
This is ideal?
Yes, ideal.
This is ideal.
Thank you very much.
Is this YouTube?
Yes, it is.
[fast forward]
Here we are.
Thank you very much.
[fast forward]
This is what the stroke is for.
I've been doing this every day.
Since birth.
Have I been born with a sloping shoulders?
I wonder.
I wonder when the stroke begins.
Fast forward.
It's strange, isn't it?
So far I haven't met anyone who's taller than me.
I've never met a Seeker.
So far I haven't met anyone who's bigger than me.
Congratulations!
I'll send it to you.
Yay!
Thanks!
LOL!
I'll buy it.
It's cute.
Cute.
I'm going to go in a little
I've never seen anything like it.
It's fresh.
Good night.
Yes, that's all.
Thank you very much.
Today's demonstration is my favorite.
I took the animals and the kimono,
I took the animals and the kimono, and for the animals, there was a fox written right here on the clothes,
I didn't use it,
I didn't use it, and I also wore a fox's merne,
I am glad that we were able to take pictures with a very cute look,
I also wore a kimono as a kataro model for Kyle's hair style,
The kimono was a color I couldn't wear at that time.
It was the first time I wore it with an orange hairstyle, so I was very happy.
It also has a big bonbon on my hair.
It was fun, but I thought it was fun to shoot for girls.
Thanks for your time.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
★Oh boy, you're so cute★
To the black ajiko spar.
I was recharging my batteries over the black papa.
I'm sorry.
That's great!
Look, daddy's charger.
I got a good shot of that.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Blacky.
You're right, I can't see it.
I'm Goo-chan.
I can't see you.
Me! Me! Gooey.
I stared!
I'll get the wish paper.
You're all mine!
It's not here.
I ate it.
It's mine.
It was all there.
It was in there, wasn't it?
It was in mine.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's... that's... that's mine.
What? But it was mine.
There were two in the desert.
I can't eat them.
He said there were two in mine, too.
I'm sure the viewers will be able to tell you that there were two in the bottle.
Oh, okay.
I had one in mine.
They were mine.
But what's yours is mine.
What's mine is mine.
No, it's not.
What's yours is mine.
No, no, no, no.
No. No. No.
No, no, no.
Suddenly I noticed his face. It's like we're father and son.
And Nanama, too.
Your mother decided to be obvious, too.
This way, I can do it.
I can do it.
Not everyone does it.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel.
Next Episode
Good morning.
Oh, are you okay now? Sorry.
Sorry.
Good morning. - Good morning.
It's Hammer.
Hammer's looks so good.
Delicious.
Very Hammer.
Guess who's from yesterday?
That's it!
Año o año o año.
When it's really over
Oh, my God.
what the hell?
Time eigen
amazing!
Thanks for your hard work
Oh, yes
Oh, you're so cute!
Oh, so cute!
Oh, he's so cute!
It's delicious, isn't it?
He's a little nervous.
I loved it.
I think you should come out.
Thank you for your time.
Time to move to the present
easy win!
I'll join you in due course
So many followers!
Thanks for all your hard work!
by H.
Cute
Cute girl
Super Cute
The end. Thank you very much.